抱歉
Sorry
对不起  请让条路
Excuse me  Make way
我的天
Jesus Christ
李氏餐馆
Li's Diner
这里有4个伤员，需要两辆救护车
There are four down, need two MS vehicles
这是什么情况？
What the hell happen here?
出车祸了？
A mobile ran them over?
没呢
No, man
刚刚这伙人打了一架
It's a fight
其中一个家伙瞬间就把其他人打趴了
One guy took them all out like seconds
那家伙还坐在里面呢
He's still in there
就是他
That's him
先生，转过身来
Turn around, Mr
把你的手放在我看得见的地方
See your hands
动作慢点
Slowly
过期的军队身份证
Military identity card  Expired
38美元
$38
还有一把牙刷
And a toothbrush
没在你身上找到家庭住址
And no home address
换句话说，你就是无家可归咯
In other words, homeless
你知道打人在这个州是二级重罪吧？你叫什么来着
Are you aware that assault is a second degree felony in this state, Mr
姓雷彻，名杰克，没有中名
Reacher  First name Jack  No middle name
如果那些被你揍的人出庭作证，刑期可延长至20年
It will extend to 20 years, once the boys you beat out there fit the testify
我们把他带到县监狱去吧
Process him  Get him to county
90秒内将会发生两件事
Two things that will happen in the next 90 seconds
你说什么？
Excuse me?
第一件事
First,
那边的那台电话将会响起
That phone there is gonna ring
第二件事
Second,
你会戴着这几副手铐，被押往监狱
You're going to be wearing these handcuffs on your way to prison
这个预言可真有意思，雷彻先生
That's one magnificent prophesy, Mr  Reacher
打电话的是宪兵110部队犯罪调查部的特纳少校
That is Major Turner of the 110th CID Military Police in Alexandria, Virginia
你们和那些被揍的家伙在进行些非法勾当
You and those boys out there made a mistake,
非法使用归属于美国军方的土地
Operating a land owned by the US army
你在胡说八道什么？
What are you talking about?
绑架非法移民
Kidnapping illegals
贩卖人口
Selling them
宪兵马上就到
MP is on the way now
如果把你们交给我处置，我绝对一枪崩了你
If it were up to me, I just kill you
电话会响到你接了它为止
She is gonna keep on ringing
我是警长，雷蒙 伍德
Sherif Raymond Wood
你究竟是谁？
Who the hell are you?
我是那些你不关注人中的一员
The guy you didn't count on
谢谢
Thank you
这里是宪兵110部队，我是李奇军士
United States army 110th, Sergeant Leach
请帮我转接特纳少校
Major Turner, please
请稍候
One moment please
我是特纳
This is Turner
是苏珊 特纳少校么？
Major S Turner?
正是，你是哪位
This is she  Whom I speaking to?
我是杰克 雷彻
It's Jack Reacher
哟，可算是等到你了
No kidding
很高兴我们终于能说上话了
Well it's nice finally speak
感觉你向我们检举揭发那个警长
Thanks for tipping to us that sheriff
其实，我
You know, I
实际上我想感谢你对我的帮助
I want to thank you for helping me
我当时情况可不太妙
I'm in tied spot
少校先生，互相帮助是应该的嘛
Isn't that what we focus to do for each other, Major?
我是前少校
Ex Major
不要在意这些细节，一日为少校，终身为少校嘛
Oh, once a Major always a Major
你现在在哪呢
Where are you calling from?
嗯，这个很难说
I said independence, I think
你自己都不知道你在哪？
You're not sure?
这不重要，我经常换地方住的
It does not really matter, I move around a lot
我听说是这样
So I've heard
关于我你还听说过什么
What else have you heard?
我听说的东西可不少呢，你在我们这算的上一个传奇了
Oh, come on, you're a legend around here
很多我手下的人还在想你怎么突然就不干了
Some folks wonder why you left
我这么说吧
Let's just say I
因为我一早起来，发现这制服尺码不太对，就不想干了
woke up one morning and the uniform didn't fit
宪兵110部，我是李奇军士
US army 110th, Sergeant Leach
杰克 雷彻呼叫少校特纳
Jack Reacher for Major Turner
请稍后
Hold on, Major
雷彻
Reacher
我的办公室如何
How's my office?
我正坐在你的办公室里呢
I'm sitting here now
你桌子上有个凹痕
There's this big dent in the desk
听说这是你某人的头按在了桌子上弄出来的
And people say you made it with someone's head
是真的么？
Is that true?
这点小事，何足挂齿
Not my finest hour
你不会又给自己招惹了什么麻烦吧？
You're not in trouble again, are you?
我知道哪怕麻烦不找上你的门
I'm afraid you have a way of finding it
你
Or
还是会给自己制造麻烦的
Looking for it
我觉得，你帮了我那么多，我应该请你吃个饭
You know, I was thinking maybe I owe you dinner for what you did
是么，吃完饭再感激我也不迟
Oh, dinner will take you a while to come to that conclusion
你什么时候来华盛顿？
When are you coming to DC?
我在去的路上
I'll get there eventually
真是很期待啊
Then I'll hold my breath
你怎么不说话了
You are not saying anything
我在想要是见到了你本人，我还会喜欢你么
I am deciding whether I'd like you in person
你喜欢哪种人？
Which way are you leaning
还没想好
On the fence
我可不觉得你能驾驭我
I'm not sure you can handle me
我并不担心这个问题
Oh, I'm not worried
是么
Hmm, worry
我觉得你多少应该有点担心的
Just a little
保重，雷彻
Take care of yourself, Reacher
我是杰克 雷彻，来找特纳少校
Jack Reacher for Major Turner
雷彻少校
Major Reacher
我是李奇军士，我们还通过话呢
Sergeant Leach, we spoke on the phone
欢迎你回来
Welcome back
叫我雷彻就好
Just Reacher
我现在没有军职
I'm a civilian now
是，先生
Yes, Sir
我带你过去
I'll take you out
很抱歉，我
Oh, I'm sorry, I was
进来，少校
Come in, Major
我是山姆 摩根
Sam Morgan
请进
Please come in  Come in
请坐
Have a sit
听说了不少你的事迹啊
Heard a lot about you
我只是顺道来拜访一下特纳 少校的
Just stopping by to see Major Turner
是么，恐怕你见不到她了
Oh, well, that's a problem
特纳少校已经被解职了
Major Turner has been relieved for command
我前几天才跟她通过话呢
I spoke with her a few days ago
她已经被逮捕了
She has been arrested
过几天在军事法庭受审
Court martials are pending
她受到了什么指控？
On what charge?
间谍罪
Espionage
在新的人选派过来之前，我暂时接替她的职务
I am assuming her duty until a replacement is assigned
还有什么我能帮你的么
Some I can help you with?
没事了，这只是一次个人访问
No  Just personal visit
你们以前就认识么
You know each other from back your old here?
不，我从没见过她
No  Never met her
少校，很抱歉把这个坏消息告诉你
Sorry to give you the bad news, Major
前少校
Ex Major
先生，我本想警告你一些事
Sir, I wanted to warn you
但是？
But?
被命令什么都不能说
Ordered not to
摩根上校直接给我的命令
Colonel Morgan directly
我觉得你还是告诉我一下为好
Maybe you should warn me now
军士，别顾虑太多
Speak freely, Sergeant
先生，特纳上校是一个好人
Major Turner is an excellent officer, sir
军方给她指派了律师么
Has she be assigned an attorney yet?
抱歉，无可奉告，先生
Ordered not to give out any information about that, sir
明白了
Understood
军士，好好遵守命令吧
Always follow orders, Sergeant
是，先生
Sir
我很好奇，你新兵营里的教官是哪位？
Just curious, who is your DI in boot camp?
格林军士
Sergeant Green, sir
打个比方，格林军士现在遇到了一些法律上的麻烦
Let's say, Sergeant Green are having legal troubles
要你给他推荐一位律师，你能做到么
Would you be able to recommend an attorney for him?
嗯
Oh
可以
Yes
我会推荐默克罗夫特上校，请他去戴尔堡的最高军事监狱，他是你能找到的最好的律师了
Definitely I recommend Colonel Moorcroft over Fort Dyer with the highest security prison you can find, sir
上校
Colonel
你是被指派为苏珊 特纳少校的律师吧？
You're the assigned council for Major Susan Turner
我是杰克 雷彻
I'm Jack Reacher
前110部队的指挥官
Former Commander of 110th
我还在想你什么时候会来找我呢
I was wondering when you are gonna show up
特纳少校要求任何情况下都不能让你见她
Major Turner requested under no circumstances you'd be granted visitation approaches
她为什么会提这种要求
Why would she say that?
也许是因为她读了你的个人档案吧
Maybe she read your file
反政府，反社会
我还反律师呢   还是个不负责任的父亲？
Anti authority, anti social
Anti lawyer   *** Dad?
你说什么？
Excuse me?
档案说你从来不肯付赡养费
says you never pay child support
我从未有过儿女
I'm not a father
有一个叫坎迪丝 达顿的女士可不这么认为
Well, a woman named Candice Darton says the differ
她联系军方，为她的女儿索要赔偿金
She contacted the army seeking compensation for her daughter
萨曼莎 达顿，现年15岁
Samantha Darton, she is 15 now
这肯定是个误会
It's a mistake
通常来说是这样
They usually are
母亲有犯罪前科，卖淫和盗窃
Mothers got two priors, prostitution and possession
这个孩子的童年都是在抚育院里度过的
The kid is in the net of foster care for whole life
你对此感觉如何？
Any feelings about that?
你问我对她在抚育院长大的看法么？
About foster care?
生活总是有诸多不顺的
Life sucks
我的意思是，你打算拿你的孩子怎么办？
I mean, the kid
她不是我的女儿，我从没听说过这个叫坎迪丝 达顿的女人
I never kid  I've never heard of Candice Darton
我来这是问你关于少校特纳的事的
I'm here about Major Turner
他们手上有什么证据
What evidence do they have?
一个硬盘
A hard drive
在她的住所搜到的，内含机密信息
Contained classified information found on Major Turner's residence
说明她正在贩卖国家机密
The inference she is selling secrets
就这些？
And that's it?
你还想要什么证据？要不要再来几张她穿着奇装异服跟塔利班成员一起吃饭的合照？
What do you want? Pictures of wearing *** or drinking with the Taliban?
她跟你说了些什么
What did she tell you?
明天之前我什么都不能说
Can't talk them until tomorrow
除非涉及公共安全
Public safety exception
真是个墨守成规的人
And you accept that?
你的法律学位在哪拿的？
Where did you get your law degree?
呵呵
Oh
上校，你可能以前是个好律师
It's possible you are once a good lawyer, Colonel
但现在就我看来，你只不过是一个要退休的蠢蛋，因为怕丢掉自己的养老金就畏缩不前
But what I see     is a retired fool who will do anything not to endanger his pension
如果你搞清楚了自己的制服所承载的责任，请告知我
Let me know when you remember what that uniform stands for
谢谢
Thank you
我们还要在这盯多久，我都饿死了
How long are we supposed to do this? I am getting hungry
耐心等就行了
Just be patient
你觉得他在吃什么
What do you think he is eating?
闭嘴
Shut up
这是你的新枪？
New gun?
对
Yep
看起来不错啊
That's nice
跟你的大手很配
Makes your hand look big
你喜欢用大枪？
Do you like big gun?
用这枪射击
Once in your face
那才叫真的爽呢
in the minute you carry on
他人怎么不见了
Where did he go?
不知道，也许是去买披萨了吧
I do not know, maybe went to pizza
你不是应该盯着他的么
You're supposed to be watching him
你是不是觉得我能眼观六路来着？
Do you think I have eyes in the back of the head?
近来如何？
How's it going?
别动
Do not!
把枪拿出来
Show me
丢到后面去
Throw back
我不喜欢有人跟踪我
I do not like being followed
一次是在人行道上
On the sidewalk before
一次是在市场里
And in the market
你就是个小偷
Your little thief
你是警察？
You're a cop?
我看起来像警察么
I look like a cop?
也许是便衣吧
** maybe
眼力可以啊
You know I'm the ***
从你的发型看出来的
It's haircut
多谢夸奖
thanks
我自己理的呢
I do it myself
估计你想做一些不正经的事吧
You're looking for something weird
再见吧
See you
你是坎迪斯 达顿的女儿吧？
Are you Candice Darton's daughter?
你想表达什么？
What did you do this time?
没事
Nothing
我只是她的一个老朋友
An old friend
是么
Yeah?
我跟你说，她已经不干那一行了
Well, she does not do that kind of thing anymore
我不是那个意思
That is not what I mean
如果你要找我妈妈，我已经不跟她一起住了
If you're looking for my mom, I do not live with her
你和谁一起住？
Who do you live with?
你说得对，少校
You're right, Major
我是要退休了
I am tired
但我并不笨
But I'm not stupid
米尔科维奇和齐蓓丽军士
Sergeant Mirkovich and Cibelli
两周前，特纳少校派他们去阿富汗开展一次调查
2 weeks ago, Major Turner dispatched them in Afghanistan in an outside investigation
他们每天都向少校递交报告
And they file reports daily
两天前，他们被人杀死在巴格拉姆军事基地
2 days ago, they were both found dead in the Bagramair base
凶手近距离射击
Shot in close range
第二天，特纳少校就被逮捕，送往监狱了
The next day Major Turner was thrown in prison
你对超源公司知道多少？
What do you know about Parasource?
超源公司？
Parasource?
它是
It is
一个很出名的军队承包商
a big note military contractor
怎么突然提起这个？
Why?
我不知道他们为什么会在这个案子里掺一脚
I do not know how did they involved in all this,
但是自从我到华府以后，他们就一直在跟踪我
but they've been following me since I got here
不管是谁杀了米尔科维奇和齐蓓丽，不管是谁把特纳上校隔离起来
Whoever killed Mirkovich and Cibelli, wanted Major Turner isolated
我觉得他们正预谋杀了她
I think they are gonna kill her too
你在说些什么？你根本没证据证明这些事是相互关联的
What are you talking about? You have no idea if any these things are related
我们得把她救出来   我的当事人并不希望你卷进这桩案件
We need to get her out    And my *** she does not want you involved
按我说的做就行了，我今晚给你打电话
Do it now  I'll call you tonight
汽车旅馆
[MOTEL]
人们在质疑提高审问技巧的价值
People questioned the value of enhanced interrogation techniques
提高审问技巧并没有什么用，但是严刑拷打确实挺管用的
Enhanced interrogation techniques don't work, but torture on the other hand, works very well
不
No
律师 委托人特免权可以追溯到英国习惯法刚出台的时期
Attorney client privilege goes back to the earliest days of English Common Law
这就意味着，特纳少校告诉了你不少保密信息
It means, Major Turner told you in confidence
其中包括她在阿富汗的调查结果
agree deal about what you learned from her investigations in Afghanistan
你给杰克 雷彻泄露了多少消息？
How much did you tell Jack Reacher?
不
No
我什么都没说
I did not talk about
当然你什么都不应该说
Of course you didn't
不
No
我们只谈了10分钟
We talked about 10 minutes
10分钟可是一段很长的时间
10 minutes is a very long time
你马上就明白这一点了
As you are about to learn
不      说！
No      Say!
说！
Say!
宪兵
[MILITARY POLICE]
杰克 雷彻么？摩根上校想见你，不知道你有空么
Jack Reacher? Colonel Morgan wants to know if you have a few minutes
你是不是不记得我了？
You do not remember me, do you?
安东尼 埃斯平？
Antony Espin?
我在这个职位上待了挺久了
Well, you will still see when I got here
你半年没通过我的提职申请
You held back my promotion for 6 months
是么，我都不记得了
Why would I do that?
因为你觉得我做决定时经常过于草率
Because you are *** to say I jump to conclusions
应该是我当时做事也太草率了吧
I'm sure I jump to conclusions
请坐
Have a sit
少校，你有选择沉默的权利
You are under no obligation to say anything, Major
前少校
Ex Mayor
昨天，你有尝试联系过特纳少校么
*** yesterday, did you try to contact Major Turner?
昨天晚上11点你去戴尔堡见过律师默克罗夫特上校么？
Did you confront attorney Col  Moorcroft at Fort Dyer at 1100?
你跟我说我什么都不用说
You told me not to say anything
我的意思是没人逼你说话，但你要回答我的问题
I said you didn't have to say anything
对
Yes
所以你确实见过他了？
Yes, you confronted him?
对，我知道我自己什么都不用说
Yes I understand I do not have to say anything
根据记录，你昨天见过默克罗夫特上校
For the record, you did confront Colonel Moorcroft yesterday
你能告诉我今天凌晨1：30 5：00之间你在哪么
Can you state your whereabouts last night at 01:30 and 05:00?
对
Yes
你倒是说啊
Yes, what?
对，我知道我自己什么都不用说
Yes I understand I do not have to say anything
少校昨天会面时把手弄伤了这一点可没有记录在案啊
Not for the record the Major has an injury to his hands at present during yesterday's meeting
真无聊，我走了
We're done here
大约在今天凌晨2：30，阿奇博尔德 默克罗夫特上校被人殴打致死
At approximately 2:30 this morning Colonel Archibald Moorcroft was beaten to death
你是我的律师咯？
You're my attorney?
我是莎莉文中尉
Lt  Sullivan
你好   你被指控谋杀律师
How do you do?   You are hereby charged with the murder of a judge *** general
他是在哪被杀的？   在他的公寓里
Where was he killed?   In his apartment
基地的公寓？   是的
Of base?   Yes
这是一起民事案件
This is an civilian matter
我只是一位平民，军队对我没有管辖权，把我交给华盛顿警方
As a private citizen the army has no jurisdiction, turn me over to the DC police
你应该知道10 75号军队条例是什么吧
You're familiar with article 10 75 of the military code?
在紧急时期，像你一样高安全级别的军官必须服从军队的召回
An officer with your security clearance remains subject to recall in an event of emergency
你离职的时候可是签字同意了的
You agree to when you sign your discharge
欢迎回到军队，少校
Welcome back to the army, Major
你现在被逮捕了
You're under arrest
[戴尔堡，最高安全监狱，华盛顿]
[FORT DYER, maximum security detention facility, Washington DC]
打开BA211门
Open BA211
[解锁]
[Unlock / OPEN]
站在那，别动
Stand here, do not move
请求转移犯人
Ask for prisoner transfer
我会申请公开你的证据
I will file for disclosure
再检查一下
Go over whatever evidence they have on you
你什么证据都看不到的
There won't be any evidence
你说什么?
What are you talking about?
他们杀了两个调查员，又杀了一个律师
They killed investigators and they killed a lawyer
证据表明你杀了特纳少校的律师   那不是我干的
Evidence suggests you kill Major Turner's lawyer    I did not kill hers
他们肯定打算杀掉我，就我所见，你也在所难逃
They are going to kill me, for I know, you're a part of it
听着，你这个呆瓜，你才是被指控谋杀的那个人
Listen, dickhead  You're the one accused of murder
你最好把证明自己无罪的证据告诉我
Wanted to show me your thread of evidence?
只有这样我才能帮你，要不然就滚吧
Then I can talk for you, otherwise go to hell
抱歉，我有点低血糖
Apologize, I have low blood sugar
你说什么？
Excuse me?
我今天早上没吃饭
I didn't eat this morning
感觉有点头晕
Felt light headed
能不能帮我去办公室找点吃的，小姐？三明治就好
Could you get me something from the office, miss? Sandwich maybe
轻打开门
open door please
进去
Move
打开BA201门
Open BA201
女士，这些人是来转移你的
Madam, these man are here to transfer you
他们是谁
Who are they?
我问你话呢，他们是谁
I ask you the question, who are they?
你说不说话？
Are you going to answer me?
雷彻？这是什么情况？
Reacher? What is this?
不许动
Hold!
这些人是来杀你的   你说什么？
These man are here to kill you    What?
他们杀了默克罗夫特
They killed Moorcroft
等等，你说什么？   昨天晚上，他死在了自己的公寓里
Wait, what?   Last night, in his apartment
现在他们要对你下手了
And now they are gonna kill you
士兵，你知道我是谁么？我要你解除戒备
Soldiers, you know who I am? I need you to stand down
女士，你的指挥权已经被解除了   没时间可以浪费了
You've relieved for command madam    No time
我无故被关在这里，你必须告诉我
I've been held without cause, it is your right to tell
这个士兵是我的人
The soldier is under my command
我们没时间可以浪费了
We don't have time for this
拿上他的军衔和文书
Get his badge and papers
我下达过明确的命令，让你别来浑水
I left explicit orders for you to stay away
命令？你居然敢命令我？   对，我就知道你会做这样的蠢事
Orders? You ordered me?   Yes, I knew you will do something like this
我希望你会后悔你当初的决定
I hope you will regret it
埃斯平，你把他怎么了？
Espin? What did you do to him?
他没事
He will be fine
这真是太疯狂了   你是说我们的晚餐泡汤了么
This is insame    This mean the dinner is off?
假装出生气的样子   不用假装，我现在确实很生气
Act angry      I'm angry,
申请囚犯转移   我是莎莉文中尉，让我进去
Prisoner transfer    Lieutenant Sullivan, coming in
打开BA211门
Open BA211
等会       让开！
Hey wait a second      Move!
他的钥匙，把他的钥匙给我
His keys, give me his keys
我的律师大概会配发到哪种车？   大概是黑色的小轿车吧
What kind of car would my lawyer be driving?   A black sedan
妈的
Damn
快！
Go!
围住这片区域 围住服务区
Secure the perimeter    Secure the service block
速度快点！   跟上！
Move! Move! Move!   Let's go!
我们得利用下那辆送餐车
Food truck
快！
Move in!
没人！
Clear
他们躲进送餐车里了！追上那辆卡车！快！
They were in the food truck! Stop that truck! Go! Go! Go!
快！
Go! Go!   Fast!
把他们抓住！
Get them out that truck!
现在情况如何？
Status?
车里没人！
Clear!
所以现在我是一位逃犯了
So now I'm a fugitive from justice
还是一位叛国者，别忘了
A traitor to your country, do not forget that
我怎么觉得你很喜欢这种感觉呢
Why do I feel like you're enjoying this?
你表达感谢的方式真是不同寻常啊
You have a very interesting way of saying thank you
那些人真的会杀了我么
Would these man really gonna kill me?
谢谢
Thank you
一群废物
Nice job
我们有一辆警车被抢了，L67号
One of our vehicles has been hijacked L67
所有单位注意，嫌疑人正驾驶着宪兵车辆L67号
All units, suspects are driving MP vehicle L67
嫌犯一号是杰克 雷彻，白人男性，持枪，十分危险
Primary is Jack Reacher, white male, considered armed and dangerous
嫌烦二号是苏珊 特纳少校，女性，身穿迷彩服，白人，现年34岁
Secondary is Major Susan Turner, female wearing military fatigues, white, age 34
你这么年轻？   闭嘴
Really?   Shut up
我们得把这车丢了，我得想办法进我的邮箱
We need to ditch this car and get into my email
大家打起精神来，他们到底去哪了
Let's go  Where the hell are they?
技术专家，打回来了么？
Spealists, have the *** call back yet?
正在呢，长官   华盛顿警方那边有消息了么
On it, Sir    Well, is there anybody heard the word from the capital police?
什么消息都可以
Anyone? Anything? A location or something?
附近有网咖么
Are there any internet cafes around here?
宾夕法尼亚北街有一家   那带我们过去吧
Pensylvania north street    Take us there, please
我真应该自己去阿富汗的
Should have gone Afganistan myself
米尔科维奇和齐蓓丽的死是我的错
Mirkovich and Cibelli were my responsibility
那不是你的错
Your job is about giving orders
在你的任期里，你手下有人牺牲么
Have you lost anyone in your watch, Reacher?
如果是在和塔利班作战时英勇牺牲，那无可厚非
My men were killed by the Taliban
但这两位是死在我们自己人手上
They were shot in the back of their head, with army issued 9mm
被人用军方派发的9毫米手枪，从背后射中头部致死
By one of our own
我一定要查明究竟是谁干的
I'll find out who did it
你手下的人在那边调查什么？
What are you guys doing over there? What are they looking for?
他们在调查一批武器的下落
Weapons
几批武器在战后废弃了
Dozens of weapons decommisioned during the war
希望它们就这么消失好了
Hopely it's gone missing
嘿，我觉得你的帽子不错
Hey, I like your hat
你也是  的粉丝么？   是啊，一直都是
U nets fan?   Yeah, from the beginning
我的调查员死后一天，他们就把我逮捕了
They arrested me the day after my investigators were killed
我的推测是，因为时差，他们应该已经把报告发到我邮箱了
Because of the time difference, they might file another report
他们把我关起来，就是不让我看到那封邮件
They locked me up so I won't see it
长官，她正尝试访问我们的系统
Sir, she is trying to access the system
把她的位置告诉我   是，长官
Give me the location    Yes, Sir
宾夕法尼亚北街
Pensylvania north street
我是摩根，准备行动吧
It's Morgan, ready to go to work, soldier?
我们已经确认他们的位置了
We've located them
他们在宾夕法尼亚北街的网咖
In an internet cafe Pennsylvania north street
干掉他们
Get it done
肯定是米尔科维奇和齐蓓丽在那边发现了什么导致他们遇害
Whatever Markovich and Cibelli found out got them killed
但是究竟是谁干的呢？
But by who?
[拒绝访问]妈的，我进不了系统
[ACCESS DENIED] Shit, they lock me out
他们可以定位我们的位置   我知道，再让我试试，可以么？
They can locate us    I know, just give me a second, ok?
他们肯定已经知道我们的位置了   让我再试试
They will know this location    Try this one    Shit
在公园的那边有一个公交车站
There is a bus stop on the other side of the park
有人跟踪我们，不是警察
We are being followed  It isn't cop
那是个职业杀手
He's a pro
在哪？
Where?
50码开外
50 yards
穿着黑色大衣，棕色头发
Black coat, brown hair
就在那边
There
现在去站台上等车就是送死
They meet us   Maybe
先去餐馆里躲躲
Restaurant
你好   我要到后面见个人
Hello    Meeting someone in the back
所有人都出去！
Everybody out!
快出去！
Out! move!   Out!
快点！
Come on, come on!
我守住这个门
I got this door
退后
Stay back
警察！不许动！
Police! Freeze!
放下武器！
Drop your weapon!
先生，我命令你放下武器！   我是宪兵
Sir, I said drop your weapon!   I'm military police!
他不是警察
He's not a cop
先生，放下你的武器
Sir, drop your weapon
我是宪兵   先生，我要你现在放下武器
I'm military police    Sir, I need you to drop your weapon
听着，转过身去，让我看到你的手
Listen, turn around and let me see your hand
好，我把我的武器放下了
I know, I am putting my weapon down
听我说，我是宪兵，他们是美国军方的两位逃犯
Listen to me, I am military police, these two are fugitives of the United States Army
先生，把你的手背到头后面   我已经转过身去了
Sir, get your hands behind your head    I am turning around
把你的手背到头后面
Place your hands behind your head
快点   我的右边口袋里有我的身份证，你可以来检查一下
Now    You can check my ID card in my right front pocket, will you just check it
检查一下你就明白了
Just check
快，让开
Go, move move move
我们两个人都没打过他
They got our signals crossed
这家伙身手不错
He's good
我们下次肯定能搞定他
We will get him next time
我承认我现在有点嫉妒正常人的生活了
Now I admit being a little jealous when we talk
想去哪就去哪，想吃啥就吃啥
Go where you want, eat when you want
不会有人命令你去做什么，或者告诉你要怎么做
Nobody tell you what to do or how to do it
军队里肯定是不可能如此自由的
It is definitely not the army way
没错
Exactly
看看那几张身份卡
Just take a look at the registration
超源公司，你觉得在厨房跟我们交手的那位是他们的人？
Parasource  You think that guy in the kitchen was one of theirs?
我猜他可能是自由杀手吧，偶尔出来接活
Freelance, it is my guess
说
Go
听说你闹的乱子不小啊
Made a mess, I hear
这家伙有点意思啊
This Reacher guy is interesting
这家伙军功章无数，不要把这次行动当成你的私人恩怨
You have no ideas they ran out of medals, so do not make this a competition
你这话说的太晚了   你确定你能自己搞定他么
Too late    Are you sure you can handle them by yourself?
我能搞定他
I can handle him just fine
那就证明你自己说的话
Prove it
咖啡   带泡沫的么？
Coffee    Cream?
不
No
尺码很合适啊
Right sizes
眼力不错
Good eyes
我们的现金用完了
Spent the rest of our cash
是时候停止逃亡，开始干活了
It's time we stop running and start hunting
我是摩根   不知道现在打电话给你时间合适么
Morgan    Catch your bad time?
我希望你是要向我投案自首
I hope you're calling to turn yourself in
我知道你在外欠债不少，我向你保证我要把你的老底挖出来
But I know you owe *** money, I promise you I'll find out
你什么都发现不了的
Nobody is going to find anything
你以为我不知道特纳少校邮件的事？
Not even major Turner's email?
看到了么？   我什么都没看到
Find it yet?   Nothing to find
那说明你看的还不够仔细
Sheer looking is not enough
干嘛废这么多话，直接看我的邮件不就完了嘛
Why don't we check my field reports?
我建议你最好不要乱动，要不然骨头折了愈合时间可就长了
It's not *** break the bones, takes longer to heal
文件上锁了，密码交出来
Locked, need the code
正在查找米尔科维奇和齐蓓丽的报告
Looking for Mirkovich and Cibelli field reports
让我们来看看你们在那边发现了什么
Let's see what do you get there, huh?
你觉得你是无敌的
You think you are invulunerable
数据拷贝中
It will be uploading
我们总会想办法抓到你的，雷彻
There are ways to get you, Reacher
搞定了
Got it
感谢你的帮忙哦
Thanks for all your help
这是米尔科维奇和齐蓓丽交给我的最后一份报告
Okay, Mirkovich and Cibelli did file a final report
我把重点念给你听
But this    okay here we go
他们最后调查过的人是一个叫做丹尼尔 普东的承包商员工
Last man they spoke to was a contractor named Daniel Prudone
他是个武器搬运工，但是现在找不到他人了
He was a weapon transporter and he disappeared
我是李奇军士
This is sergeant Leech
我是格林军士，你的老教官，记得我么
This sergeant Green, your old DI, remember me?
格林军士，听到你的声音真是太好了
Sergeant Green, so good hear from you
我现在跟你的一位老朋友在一起，我们需要你的帮助
I'm here with a friend of you, we need a favor
有一个叫做超源公司的军队承包商，你能帮我们调查一下他们背地里在搞什么名堂么？
There is a military contractor called ParaSource, could you ask around find what role they play in the backroom?
我会尽量帮忙的
I might be able to do that
还有一个叫做普东的超源公司员工，我们想知道他的下落
Also there ParaSource employees named Prudone, we need to know his whereabouts
普东，我记下来了
Prudone, copy that
军士，一切小心   是，长官
And the sergeant, carefully    Yes, Sir
雷彻
Reacher
里面没人
Clear
雷彻
Reacher
放开我！
Get away from me!
放松，你安全了
Relaxed, it's okay
你不是说过你不是警察么
You said you're not a cop?
我确实不是警察啊
I'm not
你是宪兵？   这两个是不一样的
Military police?   It's different
这辆车是你们偷得吧
But you stole this car
事情很复杂，一时解释不了   你们要带我去哪
It's complicated    Where are you taking me
我们暂时还不清楚
We do not know yet
你有手机么   你说什么？
Do you have a phone?   What?
把它给我   你们绑架我的时候，我把手机落在公寓里了
Give it to me    I left in the apartment where you kidnapped me
我们这不是绑架你
We did not kidnap you
绑架可是严重的刑事犯罪
Kidnapping is a federal offense
听我说
Look at me
有些人打算伤害你
There are people out there who want to hurt you
我想吐
I feel sick
吐到窗外吧
Throw outside the window
门打不开
It doesn't open
你上次吃东西是什么时候   我不记得了
When was the last time you had something to eat?   I do not know
我们得给她找点吃的
We need to get her some food
你画画多久了？   不知道，怎么了
How long have you drawing?   I do not know, why?
只是随口问问
Just asking
我画的不好
They suck
随你怎么说
Whatever you say
他们只不过是两个嬉皮士罢了，人那么好，谁会要杀他们呢
They are two nice Hippies, who would want to kill them
看样子你受惊不小
You has a shock
你的体内分泌了大量的肾上腺素，它们促使你决定你应该迎战还是逃跑
It's pumping adrenaline call you fight or flight
你得过一阵子才能平静下来
It's gonna take a while to calm down
我吃不下去，体内肾上腺素太多
I can't eat  I'm pumping adrenaline
我知道有个安全的地方
I know place she would be safe
什么意思？
What is that mean?
我才不要去愚蠢的学校呢
I am going to stupid school
她们有统一的服装标准，这就是她们的校服
They have a dress code, this is what they wear there
我认识那的校长，你在那很安全
I know a headmistress, you'll be safe there
校长？那是个什么东西？一个骗子么？
A headmistress? What's that? A con man?
你想活还是想死？
Do you want to live? Do you?
我想活
Yes
那你就按我们说的做，去我们叫你去的地方，直到你安全下来，明白了么？
Then you'll go where we say and stay until we say it is safe, do you understand
真是咄咄逼人啊，好吧好吧，我懂了
You are very intense, you know that? Yes, I understand
你到我这干啥   雷彻找到了那个女孩
What are you doing here?   Reacher has the girl
这不是你应该搞定的事么
You are supposed to take care of that
你们这些人，一换上便衣，就不按规矩行事了
You people, you take off the uniform and lose all discipline
他是怎么找到她的
How did he find her?
我还正想问你呢
Exactly
他们怎么这么厉害，居然找到了那个女孩
我怎么知道
How did they?   How would I know?
他今天早些时候是不是来过
If he was here earlier today?
你在监视我？你他妈的以为你是谁啊
You're watching me now? Who the hell do you think you are?
你告诉他们什么了？   你在胡说些什么
What did you give them?   What are you talking about?
你告诉他们什么了？
What did you give him?
还轮不到你来审问我
I don't have to be interrogated by guys like you
他和那个婊子到我家来，然后威胁我，我什么都没告诉他们
He came in here with that bitch and threaten me  I gave them nothing
有什么好笑的，我是花钱雇你来解决这个烂摊子的
What is so funny  We hired you to clean up this mess
你说得对
You are right
他来的时候摸过这个电话，对吧？   你想说什么？
He touch this phone, didn't he?   So?
我要是还有其它办法也不会来麻烦您了，她就在这待几天
I mean really, if I had any other choice, she would be here only for few days
没事的，不用顾虑太多
You know how we feel that here Susan
谢谢   见到你真好
Thank you    So nice to meet you
我也很高兴见到你
Good to see you too
告诉我你们的感受，你们是人，有感情，不是没生命的照相机，看到这些手你们有什么感受
Show me what you feel  You are not a camera  What do you feel about these hands
手部皮肤质量好么？ 它们是健康孩子的手么？ 皮肤上有没有什么病痛的征兆？
Are these nurturing hands? Are they health children? Do they carry pain?
欢迎来到彭布罗克学校。我叫爱莉米娅   我叫梅
Welcome to Pembroke  I'm Elemia    I'm May
我叫卡拉   跟我们走走呗
Carla    Come with us
你来这之前是在哪上学的？   我去过好几个地方
Where did you do before this?   Different places
想找一份工作真的很难
Troubles in getting job applications
你参加了那个考试么？    我打算过阵子就去考
Have you take a test yet?   I decide to do it right away
梅，你的耳环很好看，你在哪买的？
May, you earrings where did you get it
谢谢夸奖，我爸爸从纽约给我带的
Oh thank you, actually my dad bought them in New York
我妈妈答应我说带我去巴黎过圣诞节
My mother promised me we would ** when we are in Paris for Christmas
哇巴黎啊   是啊，那是个很美的城市
Paris    Yes it's beautiful
你在干嘛，还给我   你不是说你没有手机么
What are you doing?   You said you did not have a phone
你用了几次手机？    你是问我从出生开始到现在用了几次手机么？
How many time did you use this?   In my life?
我们走，拿上你的东西
Let's go, get your things
没事的，我只给一个人发了短信
Nothing, just one person
抱歉，我们得走了
Excuse me, we have to go
谢谢   等我一会
Thank you    Give me one second
发生什么了
What the hell is going on
她刚才给人发短信了   妈的，这有什么问题
She was texting    Shit, what's wrong with that?
他们可以定位追踪到这里
They could trace us
好吧，我们走
Come on, let's go
上车
Get in
讲真，这个地方真是可笑
For God's sake, that place is ridiculous
这里改变了我的一生
That place changed my life
很抱歉我用了手机
Sorry about the phone
说   我对超源公司做了点调查
Go    I'm doing some digging about ParaSource
他们有些雇员在阿富汗遇上了点麻烦
Some of their boys got into trouble in Afghanistan
在他们公司经济不景气的时候又丢了几份和政府之间的大合同
And lost some big government contracts when they are in financial trouble
为啥他能用手机？
Why does he get to have a phone?
这个丹尼尔 普东       等会 你现在安静点
Daniel Prudhomme    Hold on  You need to be quiet
抱歉，刚才说到丹尼尔 普东了，我们继续
Okay, sorry  Daniel Prudhomme  Keep going
他就是跟少校的调查员谈过话的那位公司雇员
The contractor her guys talk to
他住在新奥尔良
He lives in New Orleans
在那次谈话后他就消失了，听说是一路回家找自己的夫人和孩子了
He disappeared right after he was interrogatred  He drove back home to his wife and kids
超源公司的总部就在新奥尔良，他们知道普东已经回去了，所以在满城找他
New Orleans is Parasource's home base  And they knew he was back and they were looking for him
我们要去新奥尔良   先生，还有其它事要告诉您   说
We are going to New Orleans    Sir, something else    yes?
摩根上校死了
Colonel Morgan was killed
行凶者的凶器上发现了你的指纹
Your prints were found on the murder weapon
军士，很感谢您的帮助
Appreciate your help, sergeant
我们得抢在超源公司抓住他之前找到他
We need to find Prudhomme before Parasource gets hold him
诺福克有个机场
There is an airport in Norfolk
我们需要信用卡   还要身份证
We need credit cards    And IDs
运通卡？威士卡？
American Express?
Visa? ***
还有不少学习卡呢
SAT, extracirricular activities
这能让我们的新奥尔良之旅畅通无阻
He takes us all to New Orleans
除非你打算让我闭嘴
Unless you want me to shut up
你这小混蛋
You little shit
你确定要这么做么
Sure about this?
不    那么我来？
No    Want me to do it?
不
No
就搞定那个穿夹克的吧
10 jacket
行
Yeah
抱歉撞到你了   没事
Sorry excuse me    No problem
祝您旅途愉快
Enjoy your flight
坐在飞机的紧急安全区的旅客
You are seated in the emergency exit row
请阅读信息卡背面的相关须知
Please read your responsibility for an emergency seating on the back of the information card
信息卡在您前方的口袋里
located in the pocket in front of you
以前坐过飞机么
Hadn't flown before?
拿着
Here
你在逗我吧
You're kidding
我才不想吐呢
I'm not going to puke
那好
Good
你在军队待多久了？
So, how long have you in the army for?
待了10年吧      可以的
10 years    Oh well
你的军衔是？   少校
What's your rank?   Major
所以是不是你给人下命令
So, if you give a guy orders?
他就得遵守，比如：动作快点，对吧？
He has to obey, like fast?
是这样
Yeah
如果有人想找你的麻烦，你就用几招把他打倒，对吧？
And if he tries messing with you,you know like, all kind of moves, right?
是这样   太好了
A few    It was great
能教我几招么
Can I learn some?
当然可以
Sure
你没结婚吧？   没呢
You're not married, right?   No
你是同性恋么？ 我不歧视同性恋的，我认识不少女同
Are you gay? It's totally fine, I know many lesbian
我不是
No  I'm not gay
我还以为所有的女兵都是同性恋呢
I think all lady soldiers are gay
有些是，有些不是，军队内外一样啊
Some are  Some aren't  Like in the real world
所以，雷彻是你的男朋友？
So, Reacher is your boyfriend?
不是   那你们只是酒肉朋友？
No    Friends with benefits
不   你的意思是你不想找男朋友
No    You mean no, you don't want to
还是他不想做你的男朋友
Or, he does not want to  Your guys are really ***
好吧，我大概知道是怎么回事了
Allright, I see how it is
我的父亲也是个军人
My father was in the military
真的么
Really?
我从没见过他
Never met him
在我出生前他就走了
He left before I was born
他的驻地在哪
Where were his station?
大概是在华盛顿附近吧
Around DC, I guess
他叫什么？
What is his name?
坎迪丝从来没跟我提起过这个   坎迪丝是？   她是我妈   哦哦
我妈说我爸是个大英雄，也是个大混蛋
Candice won't talk about it    Candice?   My mom    Oh
Just say he was a big hero and a total asshole
我们马上准备降落，可以四处走动一下，如果想去洗手间的，现在可以去了
We are beginning our descend  Stretch your legs  If you want to use lavatory, use it now
我马上就回来
I will be right back
还是这种发型
Same haircut
你们这个公式的雇员都是去一家理发店么
You and your contractor go to the same barber?
检查一下手机
Check it
他现在不太舒服，你用这边这个吧
Oh, he was not feeling well  You may want to use this one
说
Go
把你手下的两个人带走吧
Take 2 after the board
你就是跟我交过手的那位吧
They were beaten
你是何方神圣？特种部队队员？
Where were you, ***? SEAL team?
差不多吧
Something like that
你什么时候回来的
When did you get back?
我经常想起以前的那些日子
I try every day
你不怀念么？
Do not you miss it?
一点也不   我觉得你内心还是很怀念的
Not a bit    I think you do
像我们这样的人
People like us
永远也无法融入到现实社会中
We can never go back to the world
我们会伤人
We hurt people
我们周围的人也因我们受伤
And the people around us get hurt
把特纳交给我，走远点，我保证不伤害那个小女孩
Leave Turner to me  Walk away now, and I won't hurt the little girl
你来新奥尔良么？
You come in New Orleans?
我会考虑一下的
I'll think about it
当心哦，我会去找你算账的   我会的
Look me out    I will
追！
Go! Go!
Go!
等等！
Wait! Wait! Wait!
我建议你们最好告诉我到底是怎么回事
Now you are going to tell me what's going on
要不然待会我可就尖叫吸引别人注意了
Or the first chance I got, I am going to scream
或者一把抓住附近的警察
Or grab a policeman!
听我说   我们是在保护你
Okay, look    We are protecting you
我发现      你
I found out that      That you do not
你能不能闭嘴
Can you stop?   Just
某些人从政府那偷了点东西   偷了什么？
Some people were stealing from the government    Steal what?
现在你知道的越少越好   放屁！
At this point, the less you know, the better    Bullshit!
这些信用卡是我的，没有它们你连飞机都上不了
I got those credit cards, okay? You are not gonna board that plane without it
他们也在追杀我
They are after me too
为什么会这样
Why?
我们得把真相告诉她
You need to tell her
他们觉得你是我的女儿
They think you are my daughter
真好笑
That's funny
你不是我的父亲   你怎么知道的
You're not my father    How do you know?
这么说吧，你凭什么觉得你是我的父亲？
Well, why do you think you are?
因为你的母亲向军方提起诉讼，说我是你的父亲
Because your mother file a complaint suit with the army claiming I was
只有一间有两个卧室的套房了，一晚350美元
All we have available is a level two bedroom suit   350 dollars
我能用现金付款么
Can I pay in cash?
所以我们要做一下亲子鉴定么
So we are gonna take a DNA test?
我们现在很忙，那些事暂且不提
We are busy right now
有些事我想告诉你
I'm goona tell you something
你可能会觉得很生气
You are gonna get angry
这一切都是个误会，都是我的错
This whole thing is my fault
此话怎讲？
How so?
提起诉讼的主意是我想出来的
I was the one who makes the file thing
希望我们家的境况能好一些
Thought she could get me out of it
你懂的，拿到了赡养费，能让我们的生活好一些
Money, child support  Help her get a life together
她出狱后情况好多了
She has got better since she got out
还找了份工作
Got a job
兴许她能自己买个小房子呢
Maybe she could get a little house
你很生气
You are mad
我能从你脸上看出来
I can see it in your face
我并不生气啊   不，你很生气
I am not mad    Yes, you are
你觉得我不过是个小孩罢了，需要人保护
You think I'm a little kid so you are worried about protect me
对
Ya
所以呢？   所以我不想待在这了
So?   So, I do not want to be here
你也不想我在这，所以我该走了
So you do not want me here  So I should just leave
可以啊，你打算去哪？
Okay  Where are you gonna go?
.  真是难忘       来吃点东西吧
And I just    Never forget  it's just      Food
终于有吃的了   谢谢
Oh, God    Thanks
饿死了，谢谢啦   没事
I am starving  thanks    Yes
她睡着了
She is out
这就是我们的晚餐约会么
Our dinner date
这香槟(实际上是可乐)喝起来还是刺骨的冷
The champagne is still chilly
我知道你是那种很浪漫的人
I knew you're the romantic type
雷彻，上次你跟我打完电话以后，你设想过会发生什么事么？
So Reacher, after those phone calls  What exactly did you think would happen?
我觉得我们能坐下来吃顿饭，喝点小酒
I think, a nice dinner  Maybe some wine
吃完饭呢？
And after dinner?
去你家吧？
Back to your place  Maybe?
还是去你的小汽车旅馆比较好
Supposed to be your city motel
永远不要低估城市旅馆的魅力
Never underestimate the charm of city motel
我懂的
I could see the appeal
也许事成之后就可以去了
What do you think we are looking for a city motel once I found Prudhomme?
我跟你一起去找普东
I'll go with you
我们中的其中一人去吧
One of us should go
我去吧
So I'll go
得留个人下来照顾她
Someone needs to stay here with her
怎么？就因为我是女的，我就要留下来照顾她？
What? Because I'm a woman? I should be the babysitter
我可不知道怎么照顾人
I do not know how to be the babysitter
你觉得我知道？   没错
Do you think that I do?   Yes
你知道么，我当兵这么久都不得不忍受这种性别歧视
You know I don't have to put up with this crap my entire career
你这呆瓜，想让我待在这，免谈，不少男军官都以为自己比我能力强
Forget it dickhead, every male officer who think they are smarter
你已经被解除指挥权了   我才是这的指挥官
You've been relieved of command    I am the commanding officer here
你不过是一个军队的逃犯罢了   你也是啊
You are the fugitive from the military justice    So did you
我们都是罪犯啊
So we are both criminals
我去吧，你待在这
I am going
少校，动手可不是个好主意
It's a bad idea, major
谢谢
thank you
普东女士
Mrs Prudhomme
听着，我已经跟你们说过了，我不知道他在哪
Look  I told you people I do not know where he is  Okay?
普东女士，我是一位宪兵   他跟你毫无瓜葛
Miss Prudhomme  I'm an MP    He is done with all of that
他需要我的保护
He needs protection
他需要我的帮助
He needed my help
是么，恐怕天王老子也救不了他
Well  He needs all the help he can get
他有没有经常联系的朋友？
Have any friends?
经常去的地方？
Places? Places he hangs out
还有你们警察都不知道的地方？
Any places that police didn't know?
你有他的照片么
Do you have a photo?
有
Ya
用完了直接烧掉吧，我不在乎
You can burn it I don't care
你们又跟踪我
You followed me in here
这是个错误
That was a mistake
你没意识到我们在监视他的老婆
You didn't think we are watching the wife
这才是个错误
That was a mistake
也许吧
Maybe
所以你想干嘛
So how do you want do this?
一个个上如何？
How about one at a time? I get a baseball bat
特纳在哪
Where is Turner?
哟，枪都掏出来了
Really
如果你们只是想杀了我，就不会现在才动手了
If you are gonna kill me, you won't have done it by now
我们不会杀了你，但我们会折磨你
We are not gonna kill you  Not until you begged for it
让你痛不欲生，只求一死
And you're going to beg
要我打左腿还是右腿？
Left or right?
特纳两分钟后会给我打电话
Turner is gonna call me in 2 minutes
如果我没接
If I do not answer it
或者是声音提起来有些异样，她就消失了，你们永远找不到她
If I don't pick up, if I sound distressed, she is in the wind
你只是在虚张声势罢了
You're bluffing
那就试试看啊
Go for it
现在你得求着我跟她好好说话了
You are goona make me talk without tipping me off
你不能折磨我，也不能杀了我
You can not torture me  You can not kill me
但你待会恐怕不得不得杀了我
And you are definitely gonna have to kill me
把手机给我，等等！
Give me the phone  Wait!
丢过来
Toss it over
伙计，轮到你了
Fellas
我跟你们说过，我讨厌别人跟踪我
I told you I don't like being followed
你完蛋了，杰克！
You're done, Jack!
杀了你还不够
killing you is not enough though
我收回我说过的话，我曾经承诺过不伤害那个小女孩
So I'm going to take back my promise about not hurting the little girl
你不会得逞的
Never gonna happen
我会的
Sure it is
总有一天，她会走在从学校回家的路上
One day, she would be walking home from school
也许她是打算出去跟人约会或者跟朋友逛街
Maybe she will be on a date or hanging out with her friends
那时我看你还怎么保护她
And you won't be there to protect her
我们再试一次，这次我要你抓住这个
Okay, let's try again  This time I want you take and hold it lower in your dress
抓住我的手，拉低，向前迈一步，转个身
So grab it  Yes, bring it low  Step out and rotate
就是这样
Nice
嘿，雷彻，看我刚刚学的那一招
Hey, Reacher, check this out
准备好了么？   开始吧
Ready?   Yes
很好
Good
你觉得怎么样
What do you think?
相信我，在你做出这种招式之前，你肯定已经死了
Trust me, before you have act like that move  We could just assume you are dead already
我们再来一次
Let's try again
待会我们再练点复杂的
We are gonna have to kick a ball into it, okay?
欢迎来到诺兰基地，我是库卓中尉
Welcome to Nolan Camp  I'm Lieutenant Kudrow
我们将竭尽所能提供帮助
We are here to help in anyway we can
查清了他们的底细么？
What do you have on them?
飞机上的那两个人以前当过兵，伤势严重
Guys on the plane were ex military  Hurt pretty bad
你知道他们为谁工作么？   他们说自己是无业人员
Do we know who they are working for?   They claim to be unemployed
我就知道他们不会老实交代的
Yes, right
给我查清他们的银行记录，服役记录，旅行记录，枪支许可证，驾驶证情况
I want their bank records, service records, foreign travels, gun registration and car registration
哪怕像他们如何煮鸡蛋，喜欢吃哪种味道的冰淇淋这样的细节也得给我挖出来
How do they like their eggs, favorite flavor ice cream  I wanted them yesterday
是，长官！
Yes, Sir!
她睡着了么？
she asleep?
我跟普东的夫人谈过了
Spoke to Prudhomme's wife
结果发现他现在是个瘾君子
Turns out he is a junkie
她不知道他在哪
She didn't know where he was
但她给了我一张他的照片
But she gave me a photo
你是因为我让你留下来照看孩子
Are you more upset that I treated you like a woman?
还是因为我对你过于粗鲁而感到生气
Or did I treated you like a man?
我很生气，因为你太自负了
I am upset because I ** you
我应该去找她的，我能搞定
I should be the one goes to talk to her  I can handle myself
我是女人，懂她的心理，能做的更好   也许吧
I could have done better    Maybe
谢谢你的道歉咯
Appreciate the apology
你什么决定都要自己做，这真的很重要么？
妈的，你真是个混蛋
Is it really so important you make every decisions?
Oh god you are such a dick
我
Okay, I
我以前一直是一个人工作
I am used to working alone, okay?
我习惯了一个人独处的日子
I used to being alone
很明显   我正试着跟你道歉
Obviously    I am trying to apologize
你继续说
Go on
你觉得我们应该怎么做
What do you think we should do?
别在我面前摆出一副屈尊俯就的样子！   我在问你的意见呢
Do not patronize me, okay?   I'm asking your opinion
我们可以去VA找他   超源公司肯定第一时间就去过了
We can go to the VA    which is the first place Parasource looked
那去当地的宪兵局问问情况？   我们肯定马上就被逮捕了
How about local MP then?   They will arrest us in a ***
雷彻，那么你的计划是什么？
Okay, then what's your plan then, Reacher?
你竟然不知道下一步该怎么办
So you do not know what to do?
你真是头脑简单，只知道打打杀杀
You are like something **** all you want is blood
你还是不明白我为什么生气吧？
You still do not get it, do you?
他们杀了我手下的人，我工作也丢了，生活全毁了
They killed my men, took away my job, my life
我不是和你一样想抓住他们，我比你更想抓住他们
I do not want them as bad as you  I want them more
看看她醒么，然后买点早饭，我们再想下一步该怎么办
Go to see if she is up  Get some breakfast and figure out the next move
你打算拿那个小孩怎么办   你又不是不知道她的名字
What would we do with the kid?   The kid has a name
我知道
I know that
你干嘛对她那么狠   生活就是这么的艰难
Why are you so tough on her?   It's a hard world
我敢肯定，她比我更明白这一点
I'm sure she knows it better
你怎么敢肯定她就明白这些道理
Do you think she knows that already
雷彻，如果她是你的亲生女儿呢？
Reacher, what if she's yours?
那我15年前真是犯了个错误
I shouldn't have been there 15 years ago
山姆？我的天
Sam? Oh man
她会去哪呢   我去穿好衣服
She is not here  And go where?   I'll get dressed
她之前有跟你说过什么吗？
Did she say anything to you?
她说她应该离开这里
She says she should leave
怎么了   你去哪了
What's up   Where were you?
我出去了   你疯了么
Out    Are you crazy?
我只是想帮你们   你要怎么帮我们呢
I'm just trying to help    How are you gonna help, huh?
你们说普东是个瘾君子   我们可没告诉过你
You guys said Prudhomme was a junkie    We never told you
我听见你们的谈话了
I heard your guys talking
街上的某些家伙说附近有流浪汉聚集地
Some dude on the street says place for homeless
大概是旧仓库厂房吧，那边消息比较灵通
Some old warehouse  People talked thing
你知道那边有多危险么？   我说过了，我能照顾好自己
Do you have any idea how dangerous that was?   I told you I can take care of myself!
你才15岁，外面正有人追杀你，知道么？
15 years old  Some people are looking for you, okay? They're looking for us
有人陪着我的
I just picked out the guy
那又怎样，所以他会保护你么？   不，至少他不会伤害我
And what, he's supposed to protect you?   No, I gave him shit
强者从不伤害他人，弱者才会那么做
Strong guys don't hurt you  The weak guys do that
强者总有个小妹妹什么的
Strong guys always have little sisters or they want one
我不知道为什么，但是事实总是如此
I do not know why, but it's just how it is
我现在太累了，去睡会
I'm really tired
我还是不理解你为什么那么做
I can not do this
你这么做真的很不明智
That was really stupid
我懂了
I know
请你别再冒那种险了
Please do not ever do that again
我这就当你是说“谢谢”了
You are welcome
嘿
Hey
我们去找他吧
Let's go find for him
[戒毒所] 抱歉，先生，你认识图片上的这个人么
[Opiate Depenency Program] Excuse me, sir, can you look at this picture, please
他可是这的常客了
*** in that circular hell
你们去那边找他吧   谢谢了
He's a vet  That's where he gonna be    Thank you
我们在找一个叫丹尼尔 普东的人,要付他一笔钱
I have money for Daniel Prudhomme
你要给他多少钱？   反正又不是给你
How much?   More than you need
你要给他多少？   你认识普东么
How much?   You know Prudhomme?
那得看你出价多少了   别拐弯抹角
Depends    It's a simple question
你找他干嘛
What do you want with him?
别问太多，告诉我就行了，我要给他钱
I told you, I want to give him money
你就是丹尼尔 普东吧？
You are Danny Prudhomme, right?
你是丹尼尔 普东吧？
Specialists Daniel Prudhomme
是的，女士   你是超源公司的员工吧
Yes, madam    You work for Parasource?
之前在阿富汗，你跟军士米尔科维奇和齐蓓丽谈过话
You spoke to two MPs, sergeant Mirkovich and Cibelli
他们在那边的基地调查过你
They interviewed you in the back room
我从没听说过他们二人
I never heard of them
听好了，米尔科维奇和齐蓓丽军士，米尔科维奇的女儿才6岁
Sergeants Mirkovich and Cibelli  Mirkovich had a 6 year old daughter
他的妻子还怀孕了，现在把事情的真相告诉我
His wife is pregnant  Now tell me what happened?
他们会杀了我的
They will kill me
你不说的话，她现在就杀了你
She would kill you
别听他瞎说，我们会保护你的，你只需要把实情告诉我就行了
No, we will protect you  You have to tell all of it
超源公司在巴格达姆基地负责护送车队
Parasource is on a truck convoy at the Bagramair
我们还负责基地的安保，我平常只需要谎报我清点的武器数量就行了
We just ran the security for the base  All I had to do just to lie the number of weapons I counted for
他给了我很大一笔封口费
He gave me shit load of money to keep my mouth shut
我们把那些武器留在那边,那些武器足够发动一场战争了
We leave that shit over there enough to start another war
超源公司没把武器运回来，而是把武器在黑市上出手，赚了不少钱
Parasource was selling that weapons instead of bringing them back to the States
后来呢？   我们跟当地军阀协商的时候出了问题
What went on?   With warlord, when we renegotiate
超源不同意他们提的条件
Parasource says no
第二天，我们车队经过一片罂粟地时被袭击了
The next day, we are driving to these poppy fields, the whole convoy just get ripped off
快下车！   我们被攻击了！
Move!   There was an attack!
我被吓坏了
I was scared shit of this
我们兵力不够，只能呼叫增援
We search for a rescue
救援队赶过来的时候有不少人阵亡
Rescuers get boy killed on the way
其中有两个我还认识呢
Two dudes I knew, man
他们调查了你之后发生了什么
What happens after you gave your statement?
我把真相告诉了他们
I told them everything
这时超源公司雇的那个杀手来了，他让我不必担心
That was this guy, he works for Parasource, he told me not to worry
他说他会搞定这些事的
He'll take care of everything
后来我只知道那两个调查员被杀了
Next thing I know that I heard they had been killed
我逃走了
I left
逃回了美国
And returned back to the States
我要是留在那肯定已经死了
I was a dead man if I stay
我
I
我从那之后就开始吸毒了
I started shooting after that
我不能回家，你知道的
I could just get myself home, you know
我放弃了我自己
I gave myself
不，你还没有完全放弃自己
But you did not
不
No
新奥尔良的毒品比那边的更多，简直是个天堂
More shit in New Orleans than they are making in Afghanistan
我感觉不太对
Something is wrong
这不合逻辑啊   什么意思？
Numbers don't add up    What do you mean?
为什么一个政府合同承包商要冒着风险在黑市上偷卖军火呢？
Why a huge government contractor risk of selling US army weapons on the black market?
超源公司可比那聪明多了   他确实聪明
Parasoure is smarter than that    He is smart, all right?
有没有人检查过箱子是不是空的？
What about   , did anybody check if the crates are empty?
估计检查箱子的人都被贿赂了
Probably, there are guys like me
我们得想办法看看箱子里有什么猫腻
We need to get inside these transports
飞机周五晚6点出发
The plane leaves every Friday at 6
6个小时飞到法兰克福，在那加好油后回来
6 hours to Frankfurt and refuel at home
我的天，那不就是今晚么
Jesus, that's tonight
“Back by 9 AM  ”
9点前回来
这边的菜放辣酱更好吃
And that's without the hot sauce
这餐不亏    先生，你好嘛
And you are gonna tell me that was worth it, sir    Hey, how are you, sir
不不，不用   我知道你想的
No, no  thanks    You know you want it
别走啊   今天不行，我身上没钱
Wait a minute    Sorry, not today  I have no money
走吧   好吧
Go on now    Okay
我的钱包呢   这些贼水平可以
Where is my wallet    Yes, I think they are good
搞定了么   像我们之前安排的那样
Did you do it?   Just like we negotiate
怎么样   搞定了
Well    It's done
打个电话给他
Make the call
是你的电话响么
Is that you?
不是我的
No sir, it's not me
这是谁的手机
Who is this?
我这有个证人，能证明我无罪
I have a witness who can exonerate me
但你得保证他的生命安全
But he has to live first
你可以过来跟我谈
Do you want to come and talk about it
你能担保他的人身安全么
Are you going to guarantee his safety?
少校，你无权指挥我
You're no longer in charge anymore, Major
你也没有指挥权，不是么，还有上级压着你吧
Neither you apparently, operative has been ahead of you this whole time
飞机里的那些人是谁？
Who are those guys on the plane, hm?
那些家伙一直想杀了我
He is trying to kill me
给你个名字你去查查， 超源公司
Here is a name for you, Parasource
再给你报几个地名
A couple of more names to think about
巴格达，是不是这些地方听起来很熟悉？
Baghdad, **, that is your first **, is it, Captain?
女士，你以为我想像现在这样么
You think I want to be in this position, madam?
我有我的本职工作，我会把它做好
I have a job to do, and I'm gonna do it
我就暂且相信你不是跟他们一伙的吧
I'll take a leap of faith that you don't have anything to do with this
看看手机背面，确保没人跟踪你以后过来
Look back of the phone, come alone make sure you're not tailed
库卓呼叫埃斯平
Kudrow to Espin
库卓呼叫埃斯平   我是埃斯平，请讲
Kudrow to Espin    This is Espin, go
我已经查到飞机上那两个人的底细了，有人通过一家设在开曼岛的壳公司给他们转账
We have digged those boys on the plane  Paid by shell company of the Cayman Islands
通过追查他们的银行记录，源头是一家军队合同承包商   超源公司？
Trace their bank accounts back to the big military contractor      Parasource
没错，你怎么知道的
Yes  How did you know that?
这你不用管了，给我把超源公司的底细查清，所有信息都给我挖出来
Nevermind, give me everything you can about Parasource, I mean everything
我正在去见证人的路上
On way to pick up my witnesses
我们给你派增援过去
We will send backup
让他们在两分钟车程外待命，听我指挥
Stand ready for 2 minutes out and wait for my signal
长官，这不符合操作流程
That was not procedure, sir
对，这不是流程，而是我的命令。雷彻反侦察意识很强，他发现有什么不对就逃走了
No, that was called an order  Reacher is good, he smells heat he will go
好的，我们就按您说的做，具体地址在哪
Allright we'll stay 2 minutes out  Where is the address?
尼克尔码头，埃斯平通话完毕
Nickel Street Wharf  Espin out
尼克尔码头
Nickel Street Wharf
在那的人统统杀掉
No witnesses
不许动
Freeze
别开枪
Do not shoot  Don't shoot man
我是来帮你的
I am here to help
你是那个证人么？   对我就是
You are the witness?   Yes, I'm the witness
你人呢
Where the hell are you?
他打消了你的疑虑么
You got what you need?
我还没跟他谈   我建议你跟他谈谈再说
Not good enough    I suggest you listen to what he has to say
我会帮你的   好的，跟我走
I can help    Okay  Let's go
现在把事情的原委告诉我吧
I like stories, tell me a story
现在我们回到万圣节长跑节目
Now we will return to the Halloween marathon
今晚游行的戏服准备好了么
Is your costume ready for tonights parade?
我来呼叫增援   去吧
I am gonna call backup    Do it
有警官手上
Officers down
我子弹打完了
I'm out
你仍然因为谋杀被通缉   是啊，我还是个杀手
You're still want of murder    That's right, I'm still a killer
我这个杀手救了你一命呢
It's why I saved you
普东把事情的真相都告诉你了么
Did Prudhomme give you a statement?
基本都说清了
Most of it
米尔科维奇和齐蓓丽也是你的朋友
Cibelli and Mirkovich were your friends
对
That's right
超源公司策划了那次谋杀
Parasource ordered their murders
恐怕他们也会对你下手
They are also trying to kill you
他们一直在给叛乱分子提供武器
They will provide insurgents with weapons
除了这个已经死了的瘾君子说的话，我们恐怕还需要更多证据
We will need more proof than the word of a dead junkie
那就得靠你帮我们了
You will help us to get it
这么办，假装逮捕我们
This  Handcuffs and take us into custody
1小时内带我们进超源公司的飞机场
Get us on the TARMAC and Parasource in 1 hour
我需要你“草率”的做个决定
I need you to jump to a conclusion, soldier
行，多谢了
Yeah  thanks
目前我调查到的情况是这样
Okay, here is what we got
6个月前，超源公司丢了几份价值数百万美元的政府合同
6 months ago, Parasource lost government contracts worth of a billion dollars
他们急需资金，银行也不愿意贷款给他们了
They are bleeding in cash, and the bank would not blood
没想到，一夜之间他们居然开始还钱给债主了
And all of sudden, they start paying back to their creditors
通过在黑市上卖军火，他们能挣多少钱？
How much money can they really make by selling weapons on the black market?
就算M4步枪5000一把，火箭筒2500一把
M4 for 5 thousand dollars, a rocket launcher half of that
跟政府订单比起来这些小钱都不算啥啊
That's nothing compared to government contracts
他们的钱从哪来的呢
So where did they get the money?
这里是宾馆前台，有什么需要帮助的么？
Guest services, how can I help you?
请问你们提供客房服务么？
Hey, do you have room service?
抱歉，我这边的记录显示你是用现金付的房费，如果没有信用卡不能给你送餐
I'm sorry I see you pay cash for your room, I'm afraid we can't provide instant dinner without a credit card
我有信用卡，等一下
Uh, yes  Hold on a second
你应该知道万圣节游行就要开始了吧，要过会才能给你送过去
You do understand that the parade is coming and it may take a while
没问题，尽快就好，我要饿死了
Em, it's fine, I'm starving
维萨卡可以么？
Eh, visa ok?
长官，有人使用我们正在监视的被盗信用卡消费了
Sir, we got a hit on one of those stolen cards
消费地点位于达菲宾馆，皇家街10 18号
Hotel Daphine, 10 18 Royal Street
找到那个女孩了
It's the girl
我已经警告过他了
I've warned him
请出示您的证件
Identity card
安东尼 埃斯平上尉，宪兵110部队
Captain Anthony Espin 110 military police
我要通报一下
I'm gonna call this in
他们正在装货，我们要抓紧时间进去
They are loading the crates  We are gonna get in there
这次的行动内容是什么，少校？
What's drill, Major?
行动内容是，维护正义
Drill is enforcing the law
请各位系好安全带
Seat belts, please
少校，看你的了
Turner    Major
最后警告一次
Hey, this is your last warning
趴在地上
On the ground now
都别开枪
Easy
立刻放下武器
Drop your weapons immediately
伙计们，放下武器
Weapon down, boys
放下武器
Put them down  Take them down
What is going on here？
究竟是怎么回事
You're in charge of this operation？
你是这次行动的负责人？
我是詹姆斯 哈克尼斯将军，这家公司归我经营
I was General James Harkness, I run this company
我们有理由相信这里有人正在进行违法行为
We have probable cause to believe a crime has been commited
And you are？
你是哪位？
苏珊 特纳少校，宪兵110部队
Major Susan Turner 110 Military Police
就是那个被指控为间谍的宪兵特纳少校？
The Major Turner one of the MPs accused of espionage?
你是想说我们都是间谍么？
You mean these MPs?
这些箱子里本应装着属于美国军方的武器
This crates are supposed to contain the weapons belonging to the US armies
事实上你背地里把这些武器卖给叛乱分子
In fact you sold them to insurgents
所以这些是空箱子
And these are now empty
你知道我是谁么，少校？
Do you know who I am, Major?
是的，将军，我知道
Yes  General  I know
你就是那个应该为我两位手下之死负责的人
You're the man responsible for the death of two of my man
现在打开箱子，接受检查
Now open up those crates
要不然等我抓着你的头发，一巴掌扇在你脸上就不太好了
before I grab you by your hair plugs and bitch slap that smug look of your face
根据货物清单，箱子里有什么货物？
What does the manifestors say in there?
84毫米口径火箭筒，长官
84 mm rocket launcher sir
打开这个箱子
Open it
打开吧
打开那个箱子
Open that one
Open it!
打开吧
Open it
打开那个箱子
Open that one
听不懂我说的话么，打开那个箱子！
I said open up that crate!
打开吧
Open it
中尉，做好你的本职工作，给我逮捕这个臭女人
Litenauant, do your goddamn job and place this goddamn woman under arrest
抱歉，少校
Sorry Major
你得跟我走
You are gonna need to come with me
你说的对
You are right
这说不通
The numbers don't add up
长官
Sir, sir
拦住那个家伙
Stop that man
雷彻   拦住他
Reacher    Stop that man
拦住他
Stop him!
干掉他，马上！
Take him down, now!
兄弟，别乱动
Deep breath, son
高纯度鸦片
Pure opium
现在说的通了
Now the numbers add up
把他带走吧
Get him out of here
你好
Hello
晚上好，我在找一男一女两个成年人，带着一个金发的小孩
Good evening, I'm looking for a man and woman, and a little blonde teenager
抱歉，我不能给你提供他们的信息
Sorry, I can not help you that
我在找两个成年人，一个金发女孩
I'm looking for two adults and a little blonde girl
把他们的房门钥匙给我
Take the key
已经把将军逮捕了，这儿的鸦片大概有500公斤吧
Take him in custody  It weighs nearly 500 kg
山姆
Sam
雷彻，他来找我了，他在这   你说什么？
Reacher, it's him  He is here    What?
在宾馆，快来救我
At the hotel, hurried
山姆，听我说
Sam, listen to me
山姆
Sam
你是谁？你在干什么？
What? Wait! Excuse me! Hey! Where are you doing?
你在干什么？
Hey, where are you doing?
你要去哪，快回来
Where are you going, come back here!
她不接电话
She is not answering
再试几次
Try again
小心车！
Car! Car!
山姆！
Sam!
她肯定不在宾馆里，跑到街上去了
She is not in the hotel  She is on the street
你怎么知道的
How do you know?
换做是我，我也会这么做
Because that's what I would do
我们分头找
I'll go this way
找到了她在哪么   我找了三家宾馆，根本找不到她
她肯定是躲在哪了
Did you see anything?    Three more hotels  We didn't find a trace, nothing
She is got to be somewhere
雷彻
Reacher
我们来做个了断吧，就我们两个
Let's finish this  Just you and me
等抓到了你那可爱的小女孩，我要好好的调教一下她
I'm going to have some fun with the pretty little girl
她不是我女儿
She's not my little girl
是么，怎么你的声音里充满了恐惧呢
Is that fear in your voice, Jack?
我要将你碎尸万段
I am going to break your arms, your legs, your neck
我对此感到非常兴奋
What you hear is an excitement
嘿，你别待在这
Hey, you! Get out of there! Come on
借着跟你聊天的当，杰克，我终于找到了一种能让你痛不欲生的方式，能让你痛不欲生
Nice try, Jack  I find a way to hurt you like you've never felt before
萨曼莎！
Samantha!
你找到她了吗？
You have her
波特街，拉菲宾馆附近
Porter street, Laffey Hotel
萨姆快跑！
Sam, run! run!
你敢开枪打我，她就会掉下去
Shoot me and I will let go
来啊，开枪打我啊，杰克
Shoot me  Shoot me, Jack!
开枪打我啊！
Well, shoot me!
超源公司已经完蛋了
Parasource is done
哈克尼斯已经被逮捕了
Harkness is in custody
恭喜啊，杰克
Congratulations, Jack
我他妈根本不在乎
I really don't give a shit
别哭了
Shut up!
给我闭嘴
我早就警告过你了，我会对她下手
I told you, this would happen
你不是说要在我们之间来个了断么
You said this was about you and me?
把枪放下
Put the gun down
好好好
Okay, okay
我把枪放下
Okay
如果我把枪放下了，你就放她走
If I put down the gun, you let her go
我的命换她的命
My life for hers
不要！
No!
这个主意好
I like it
就这么办
Deal  Jack
没事的，萨姆，看着我
It's ok,Sam  look at me
没事的
It's ok
我们别无选择
It's the only way
没事的
It's okay
我现在要把枪放下了
I'm going to put the gun down now
你知道这意味着什么吗
You know what this means?
这意味着，我们早就死了
It means we're dead already
把枪弄过来
Over here
用脚踢过来
Kick it over here
看我这
Look at me
You look at me!
嘿
Hey
他还好么？   应该吧
Is he okay?   Yes, I think so
雷彻，看我这
Reacher, look here
我在这呢
I am right here
你能走动么
Can you walk?
我没问题
Sure
慢点
Easy
伙计，你可是从一栋楼上摔下去了啊   我知道
Dude, you jump off a building    I know
疼么   还好
It hurts?   Yes
你知道这楼多高么   我们能换个时间再讨论这个话题么
Did you see how high it was?   Can you possibly have this conversation some other time
谢谢你
thank you
我觉得简直太逗了，你到这明明是来找我，却意外收获了另外一位女孩
You know, it's funny  You come here looking for one girl and you end up with another
我还存着你的电话号码呢
I still got your number
再见，雷彻
Bye, Reacher
再见
Major
欢迎回来，少校
Good to see you back, Major
谢谢你，上尉
Thank you, Captain
抱歉，我堵车了
Sorry  I'm stuck in traffic
哟还换了新的T恤衫啊
New T shirt
真多嘴
Shut up
谢谢你愿意过来
Thanks for coming
所以，雷彻
So, Reacher
你到底是不是我的父亲？
Are you my father or not?
等你妈妈来的时候我们就知道了
We will just see when your mother gets here
你还认得她么？
So you recognize her
我睡过的每个女人我都记得
I tend to remember the women I slept with
估计她会记得你吧   希望如此
I think she will remember you    Thanks a lot
你并不是我的父亲
You're not my father
为什么这么说？
Why do you say that?
看到了那边那个服务员么
See that woman over there?
她给你添了三次咖啡
The waitress who refills your coffee three times
那个就是我母亲
That's her
你根本没有表现出认识她的样子
You have no idea who she is
我一直都知道你不是我父亲
I knew it all along
恐怕你也是那次吃饭的时候才知道的吧
No, you didn't
你肯定如释重负吧
I'm sure you are relieved
并没有
Not really
把这事忘了吧
Just let it go
我会慢慢忘记的
I will try
你不会觉得孤单么
Do not you ever get lonely?
偶尔吧
Sometimes
偶尔会觉得孤单
你寂寞了可以给我打电话
You can call me when you do
所以
So
你要走了吧？
Should you leave?
对
I'd better go
我要上课了
I got class
好好学 你在画画方面真的很有天赋
Just keep that up, because you are really good at it
真的
You're really good
好好学，情况会好起来的
You will ok then
那么
Well
有机会再见，雷彻
See you around, Reacher
想我了么？
Miss me yet?